Guide to the Fred W. Voget Papers 1935-1996
Maureen and Mike Mansfield Library, The University of Montana--Missoula
- Photos, 1939-1989; Series VI; 2.5 linear feet
  - Grandchildren of Annie Bear Below, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Grandchildren of Annie Bear Below? (Box-folder 24/77, Photo number 318(VI):334)
  - Modern Crow cradleboard, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/78, Photo number 318(VI):335)
  - Waiting for a turn at the giveaway, Frederick and Ira Lefthand in the middle, 1987 (Box-folder 24/79, Photo number 318(VI):336)
  - Frederick seated with a picture of his father above, 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Frederick Left Hand with a picture of his Father (Pete Lefthand) above. (Box-folder 24/80, Photo number 318(VI):337)
  - Dexter Falls, Down and his wife, 1986; [From Aaron Brien] Dexter Falls Down and Magdaline Little Nest. (Box-folder 24/81, Photo number 318(VI):338)
  - Dexter Falls Down Family, Crow, 1986 (Box-folder 24/82, Photo number 318(VI):339)
  - Anthony, Agnes, and family at the district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/83, Photo number 318(VI):340)
  - District championship arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, June 1987; [From Aaron Brien] District Championship Arrow Throwing. Lodge Grass, Montana. (Box-folder 24/84, Photo number 318(VI):341)
  - Action at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/85, Photo number 318(VI):342)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/86, Photo number 318(VI):343)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/87, Photo number 318(VI):344)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/88, Photo number 318(VI):345)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/89, Photo number 318(VI):346)
  - View of arrows thrown at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/90, Photo number 318(VI):347)
  - View of arrows thrown at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/91, Photo number 318(VI):348)
  - Boy holding arrows at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Looks like Dean Don’t Mix. (Box-folder 24/92, Photo number 318(VI):349)
  - Frederick Lefthand and Ralph Good Luck with drumstick, June 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Ralph Good Luck (Duuptakaish Chiwaakuush, High Bald Eagle) and Fredrick Left Hand (Seizes the Living Bison Bull). (Box-folder 24/93, Photo number 318(VI):350)
  - A future arrow thrower at junior arrow throw competition, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/94, Photo number 318(VI):351)
  - Spectators at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/95, Photo number 318(VI):352)
  - Group photo at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, June 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Lodge Grass District champion arrow throwing. (Box-folder 24/96, Photo number 318(VI):353)
  - District team tents at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/97, Photo number 318(VI):354)
  - Setting up goal for district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/98, Photo number 318(VI):355)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/99, Photo number 318(VI):356)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/100, Photo number 318(VI):357)
  - Contestants getting ready at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/101, Photo number 318(VI):358)
  - District arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/102, Photo number 318(VI):359)
  - Pryor district tent at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/103, Photo number 318(VI):360)
  - Frederick Lefthand at district arrow throw, 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Frederick Left Hand (Seizes the Living Bison Bull), Arrow Throwing tourney. Lodge Grass, Montana. (Box-folder 24/104, Photo number 318(VI):361)
  - Judge's stand at district arrow throw, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/105, Photo number 318(VI):362)
  - Seeing who won at district arrow toss, Lodge Grass, Montana, June 1987; [From Aaron Brien] This last throw was to see who won the District arrow throwing. (Box-folder 24/106, Photo number 318(VI):363)
  - Cottonwood trees along Little Big Horn near Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 24/107, Photo number 318(VI):364)
  - Location where peyotists get sand for altar, north of Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Puuxkalachiliá Alasáthe (Sand Creek). Some peyote church members come here to get sand for their alters. North of Lodge Grass, Montana. (Box-folder 24/108, Photo number 318(VI):365)
  - Jim Old Crow and others at Lodge Grass camp, undated (Box-folder 24/109, Photo number 318(VI):366)
  - Catholic Church, Lodge Grass, Montana, undated (Box-folder 24/110, Photo number 318(VI):367)
  - Church of Latter Day Saints, undated (Box-folder 24/111, Photo number 318(VI):368)
  - Catholic Church, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Our Lady of Loretto Catholic Church, Lodge Grass, Montana. (Box-folder 25/1, Photo number 318(VI):369)
  - Sign advertising sun dance, 1987 (Box-folder 25/2, Photo number 318(VI):370)
  - View of sun dance camp at Pryor, Montana, 1986 (Box-folder 25/3, Photo number 318(VI):371)
  - Sun dance at Pryor, Montana, 1986 (Box-folder 25/4, Photo number 318(VI):372)
  - Frederick Lefthand at sun dance, Pryor, Montana, July 1986; [From Aaron Brien] Fredrick Lefthand (Seizes the Living Bison Bull) at Pryor sundance. Pryor, Montana. (Box-folder 25/5, Photo number 318(VI):373)
  - Ira Lefthand at sign advertising Sioux "cutting" sun dance, 1987; [From Aaron Brien] Ira Lefthand's Crow name was" Chief Lazy." This name his dad Pete purchased from Dick Day Light. (Box-folder 25/6, Photo number 318(VI):374)
  - Some negative strips from sun dance giveaway and district arrow throw, 1987 (Box-folder 25/7)
  - Negatives from district arrow throw photos, Lodge Grass, Montana, 1987 (Box-folder 25/8)
  - Robert Yellowtail in traditional dress, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Robert YellowTail (Biawakshash, summer) (Box-folder 25/9, Photo number 318(VI):375)
  - Yellowtail Dam, Montana, July 18, 1987 (Box-folder 25/10, Photo number 318(VI):376)
  - Landscape with low hills in background, 1940 (Box-folder 25/11, Photo number 318(VI):377)
  - Teepee in far background, 1940 (Box-folder 25/12, Photo number 318(VI):378)
  - IXL Ranch, Tongue River Canyon, WY, 1940 (Box-folder 25/13, Photo number 318(VI):379)
  - Unknown landscape, 1940 (Box-folder 25/14, Photo number 318(VI):380)
  - Unknown landscape, 1940; [From Aaron Brien] Baahupuuo, shoot the rock. Commonly known as Castle rocks. These rocks are known to be the home of the "Little People." The story of the "Lost Boy and the Little People" explains this. (Box-folder 25/15, Photo number 318(VI):381)
  - Line of people and cars in distant background, undated (Box-folder 25/16, Photo number 318(VI):382)
  - Line of people and cars in distant background, undated (Box-folder 25/17, Photo number 318(VI):383)
  - Unknown landscape featuring a lake, undated (Box-folder 25/18, Photo number 318(VI):384)
  - Unknown landscape, 1940 (Box-folder 25/19, Photo number 318(VI):385)
  - Look-out type view of unknown landscape, undated (Box-folder 25/20, Photo number 318(VI):386)
  - View of down slope, 1940 (Box-folder 25/21, Photo number 318(VI):387)
  - Cottonwood trees, 1940; [From Aaron Brien] Two non-Indian children in grove of cottonwood trees. (Box-folder 25/22, Photo number 318(VI):388)
  - View of semi-forested slopes, 1940 (Box-folder 25/23, Photo number 318(VI):389)
  - View of small hills above pasture, 1940; [From Aaron Brien] View of the Castle rocks. Pryor, Montana. (Box-folder 25/24, Photo number 318(VI):390)
  - Cottonwood trees, 1940 (Box-folder 25/25, Photo number 318(VI):391)
  - Cottonwood treetops, 1940 (Box-folder 25/26, Photo number 318(VI):392)
  - Distant view of vehicle on dirt road, 1940 (Box-folder 25/27, Photo number 318(VI):393)
  - Cattle in rough pasture with mountains in background, 1940; [From Aaron Brien] Horse on rough pasture. Looks like the southern side of the Pryor Mountains. (Box-folder 25/28, Photo number 318(VI):394)
  - Unknown landscape, 1940 (Box-folder 25/29, Photo number 318(VI):395)
  - Unknown landscape with sagebrush, 1940 (Box-folder 25/30, Photo number 318(VI):396)
  - Road through small trees and brush, 1940 (Box-folder 25/31, Photo number 318(VI):397)
  - Landscape, 1940 (Box-folder 25/32, Photo number 318(VI):398)
  - Landscape, 1940 (Box-folder 25/33, Photo number 318(VI):399)
  - Horse and barns, undated (Box-folder 25/34, Photo number 318(VI):400)
  - House among trees, undated (Box-folder 25/35, Photo number 318(VI):401)
  - Rock canyon, undated (Box-folder 25/36, Photo number 318(VI):402)
  - Possible old fire pit, 1940 (Box-folder 25/37, Photo number 318(VI):403)
  - Possible old fire pit, 1940 (Box-folder 25/38, Photo number 318(VI):404)
  - Six unknown people at table, undated (Box-folder 25/39, Photo number 318(VI):405)
  - Man, woman, and children, 1940 (Box-folder 25/40, Photo number 318(VI):406)
  - Lodge Grass grade school staff (includes Fred Voget), circa 1940-1941 (Box-folder 25/41, Photo number 318(VI):407)
  - Unidentified man and woman, Boulder, Montana, 1942 (Box-folder 25/42, Photo number 318(VI):408)
  - Man standing by remnants of teepee ring, undated (Box-folder 25/43, Photo number 318(VI):409)
  - Man sitting by pile of stones, undated (Box-folder 25/44, Photo number 318(VI):410)
  - Man standing on pile of stones, undated (Box-folder 25/45, Photo number 318(VI):411)
  - Man in distance, undated (Box-folder 25/46, Photo number 318(VI):412)
  - Bowl, undated (Box-folder 25/47, Photo number 318(VI):413)
  - Top view of bowl, undated (Box-folder 25/48, Photo number 318(VI):414)
  - Bowl, undated (Box-folder 25/49, Photo number 318(VI):415)
  - Bone and bead display, undated (Box-folder 25/50, Photo number 318(VI):416)
  - Arrowheads, undated (Box-folder 25/51, Photo number 318(VI):417)
  - Arrowheads, undated (Box-folder 25/52, Photo number 318(VI):418)
  - Arrowheads, undated (Box-folder 25/53, Photo number 318(VI):419)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/54, Photo number 318(VI):420)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/55, Photo number 318(VI):421)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/56, Photo number 318(VI):422)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/57, Photo number 318(VI):423)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/58, Photo number 318(VI):424)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/59, Photo number 318(VI):425)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/60, Photo number 318(VI):426)
  - Arrow or spear heads, undated (Box-folder 25/61, Photo number 318(VI):427)
  - Grinding stone, undated (Box-folder 25/62, Photo number 318(VI):428)
  - Ax heads, undated (Box-folder 25/63, Photo number 318(VI):429)
  - Ax heads, undated (Box-folder 25/64, Photo number 318(VI):430)
  - Ax head, undated (Box-folder 25/65, Photo number 318(VI):431)
  - Stone artifacts, undated (Box-folder 25/66, Photo number 318(VI):432)
  - Stone artifacts, undated (Box-folder 25/67, Photo number 318(VI):433)
  - Saddle, undated (Box-folder 25/68, Photo number 318(VI):434)
  - Saddle, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Indian saddle from top view. (Box-folder 25/69, Photo number 318(VI):435)
  - Stones with carved dates and locations, undated (Box-folder 25/70, Photo number 318(VI):436)
  - Bowl and possible jewelry, undated (Box-folder 25/71, Photo number 318(VI):437)
  - Beaded tomahawk pendant, undated (Box-folder 25/72, Photo number 318(VI):438)
  - Beaded tomahawk pendant, undated (Box-folder 25/73, Photo number 318(VI):439)
  - Decorated and woven hide, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Painted raw parfleche. (Box-folder 25/74, Photo number 318(VI):440)
  - Constructing sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Inside view of sundance lodge. From what I see it looks like the last major event to happen in the sundance. When a dancer ask someone to come in the lodge and pray from them just before everyone walks out together. (Box-folder 25/75, Photo number 318(VI):441)
  - People outside of sun dance lodge, undated (Box-folder 25/76, Photo number 318(VI):442)
  - Horse in foreground, crowd gathered for sun dance, undated (Box-folder 25/77, Photo number 318(VI):443)
  - Seated and walking groups, undated (Box-folder 25/78, Photo number 318(VI):444)
  - Children observing adult conversations, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Give Away Ceremony, children in the foreground. (Box-folder 25/79, Photo number 318(VI):445)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men praying at the Center Pole. (Box-folder 25/80, Photo number 318(VI):446)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men praying at the Center Pole. (Box-folder 25/81, Photo number 318(VI):447)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men dancing in lodge. (Box-folder 25/82, Photo number 318(VI):448)
  - Two men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Old woman being doctored at the center pole. (Box-folder 25/83, Photo number 318(VI):449)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men praying at the Center Pole. It is common for sundancers to pray while standing at the center pole. They pray to the creator for strength and also the for the reason they have decided to dance in the lodge. (Box-folder 25/84, Photo number 318(VI):450)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men dancing in the lodge. (Box-folder 25/85, Photo number 318(VI):451)
  - Full view of center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men focused on the Center Pole while dancing. Many sundancers among the Apsaalooke are told "the Center Pole is everything you want in life, stay focused and always push through and you'll get it." (Box-folder 25/86, Photo number 318(VI):452)
  - Men looking up at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Men focused on the Center Pole while dancing. (Box-folder 25/87, Photo number 318(VI):453)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated (Box-folder 25/88, Photo number 318(VI):454)
  - Men at center pole in sun dance lodge, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Dancing to the pole. (Box-folder 25/89, Photo number 318(VI):455)
  - Caughnawaga men, mostly steelworkers home for the weekend, undated (Box-folder 26/1, Photo number 318(VI):456)
  - Two men standing outside of Chief Poking Fire Indian Museum, Caughnawaga, Quebec, Ontaria, 1950 (Box-folder 26/2, Photo number 318(VI):457)
  - Chief Poking Fire compound, Caughnawaga, Quebec, Ontario, 1950 (Box-folder 26/3, Photo number 318(VI):458)
  - Chief Poking Fire Museum, Caughnawaga, Quebec, Ontario, 1950 (Box-folder 26/4, Photo number 318(VI):459)
  - Entrance of Chief Poking Fire Museum, Caughnawaga, Quebec, Ontario, undated (Box-folder 26/5, Photo number 318(VI):460)
  - Two-story house, Six Nations, undated (Box-folder 26/6, Photo number 318(VI):461)
  - Min Jamieson with Chow dogs, Six Nations, undated (Box-folder 26/7, Photo number 318(VI):462)
  - Min Jamieson in Indian dress, circa 1963 (Box-folder 26/8, Photo number 318(VI):463)
  - George Jamieson, Barbara, and Dave Moses, Six Nations, undated (Box-folder 26/9, Photo number 318(VI):464)
  - Jo Martin, his wife Maggie, and nephew at Caughnawaga home, 1967 (Box-folder 26/10, Photo number 318(VI):465)
  - Jo Martin in front of Caughnawaga long home, undated (Box-folder 26/11, Photo number 318(VI):466)
  - Mohawk school, Six Nations, Oshweken, Ontario, undated (Box-folder 26/12, Photo number 318(VI):467)
  - Crypt of Joseph Brant near Brantford, Ontario, undated (Box-folder 26/13, Photo number 318(VI):468)
  - Grandchildren of Chief Deskahe, circa 1963 (Box-folder 26/14, Photo number 318(VI):469)
  - Children of Dave and Barbara Moses, Six Nations, circa 1962 (Box-folder 26/15, Photo number 318(VI):470)
  - Church where 1703 Queen Anne's plate is held, Six Nations, near Brandford, Ontario, circa 1962 (Box-folder 26/16, Photo number 318(VI):471)
  - Church where 1703 Queen Anne's plate is held, Six Nations, near Brandford, Ontario, circa 1962 (Box-folder 26/17, Photo number 318(VI):472)
  - Old barn and wagon, Six Nations, Oshweken, Ontario, undated (Box-folder 26/18, Photo number 318(VI):473)
  - Nellie Scott, Arapahoe, with two dogs, undated (Box-folder 26/19, Photo number 318(VI):474)
  - Elk trained by Nellie Scott, Arapahoe, undated (Box-folder 26/20, Photo number 318(VI):475)
  - Nellie Scott, Arapahoe, in traditional dress, 1948 (Box-folder 26/21, Photo number 318(VI):476)
  - Nellie Scott (L) in traditional dress standing with unidentified woman, undated (Box-folder 26/22, Photo number 318(VI):477)
  - Hungerian Imre Nag in Cheyenne Indian attire with son, David, 6 years old, 1987 (Box-folder 26/23, Photo number 318(VI):478)
  - Group of Hungerian Plains Indians, Imre Nag (center) conducting marriage ceremony, 1983 (Box-folder 26/24, Photo number 318(VI):479)
  - Photo of war lodge drawing, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Photo of a War lodge (Ashdaache) drawing. In the Apsaalooke language the word Ashdaache means "the lodge that leans." (Box-folder 26/25, Photo number 318(VI):480)
  - Photo of picture of defensive rifle pit, undated (Box-folder 26/26, Photo number 318(VI):481)
  - Unidentified crowd of people in front of church, circa 1950s (Box-folder 26/27, Photo number 318(VI):482)
  - Custer, two other white hunters, and Indian with grizzly bear carcass, 1874; [From Aaron Brien] Bloody Knife, General Custer and William Ludlow (far right) kill grizzly bear. Black Hills. (Box-folder 26/28, Photo number 318(VI):483)
  - White Arm's camp at Sheridan, Colorado Historical Society photo, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Apsaalooke Camp. This looks like a postcard of an early crow fair. (Box-folder 26/29, Photo number 318(VI):484)
  - Postcard title "Crow Indian Village", October 16, 1941; [From Aaron Brien] Post card of Ashdaache (War Lodge). (Box-folder 26/30, Photo number 318(VI):485)
  - Postcard of war lodge, undated (Box-folder 26/31, Photo number 318(VI):486)
  - Postcard of Sitting Bull and Buffalo Bill from photo originally taken in 1885, undated (Box-folder 26/32, Photo number 318(VI):487)
  - Postcard of Medicine Crow from photo originally taken in 1880, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Medicine Crow (Paalatchiwaaxpaash or Sacred Raven.) War leader and Chief of the Kicked in the Belly Band of Apsaalooke. (Box-folder 26/33, Photo number 318(VI):488)
  - Postcard of Swallow Bird, an Apsaroke Crow, from photo originally taken in 1908, undated (Box-folder 26/34, Photo number 318(VI):489)
  - Postcard of Crowchild, Shiptella, from photo originally taken in 1900, undated (Box-folder 26/35, Photo number 318(VI):490)
  - Postcard titled "How Custer Fell", 1913; [From Aaron Brien] White Man Runs Him, Hairy Moccasin, Curly and Goes Ahead. Apsaalooke Scouts stand near the place of Custer's death. (Box-folder 26/36, Photo number 318(VI):491)
  - Postcard of Sitting Bull from photo originally taken in 1864, undated (Box-folder 26/37, Photo number 318(VI):492)
  - Card of "Lone Tree," an Apsaroke Crow from photo originally taken in 1908, undated; [From Aaron Brien] Post Card of "Long Tree," an Apsaalooke man. (Box-folder 26/38, Photo number 318(VI):493)
  - Postcard of Edward Sheriff Curtis from photo taken in 1899, undated (Box-folder 26/39, Photo number 318(VI):494)
  - Postcard of Native American woman, undated (Box-folder 26/40, Photo number 318(VI):495)
  - Postcard titled "The Circle", undated (Box-folder 26/41, Photo number 318(VI):496)
  - Postcard titled "Kilauea by Day", undated (Box-folder 26/42, Photo number 318(VI):497)
  - Postcard titled "Respect for Elders", undated (Box-folder 26/43, Photo number 318(VI):498)
  - Postcard of wagon train on rocky mountain road, undated (Box-folder 26/44, Photo number 318(VI):499)
  - Postcard of Crow Indians posed in traditional dress, undated (Box-folder 26/45, Photo number 318(VI):500)
  - Postcard of Crow Indian wearing traditional dress, mounted on horse, undated (Box-folder 26/46, Photo number 318(VI):501)
  - Postcard of teepee, undated (Box-folder 26/47, Photo number 318(VI):502)
  - Cartoon-style postcard titled "Out Where the West Remains", undated (Box-folder 26/48, Photo number 318(VI):503)
  - Postcard of bison, brown and white, undated (Box-folder 26/49, Photo number 318(VI):504)
  - Postcard titled "Southern Peaks of Presidential Range from Mt. Washington, undated (Box-folder 26/50, Photo number 318(VI):505)
  - Postcard of "Crow Indians Firing into the Agency" by Frederic Remington, undated (Box-folder 26/51, Photo number 318(VI):506)
  - Postcard of "Geronimo and his Band Returning from a Raid in Mexico," by Frederic Remington, undated (Box-folder 26/52, Photo number 318(VI):507)
  - Postcard of "Suspicious Guests" drawn by Henry F. Farny, undated (Box-folder 26/53, Photo number 318(VI):508)
  - Postcard of Crow Fair, 1989 (Box-folder 26/54, Photo number 318(VI):509)
  - German postcard of possible native head dress, undated (Box-folder 26/55, Photo number 318(VI):510)
  - German postcard of brightly colored native artifact, undated (Box-folder 26/56, Photo number 318(VI):511)
  - Postcard of two present day soldiers' bronze statues, undated (Box-folder 26/57, Photo number 318(VI):512)
  - Crow butchering buffalo, negative only, circa 1970s (Box-folder 26/58, Photo number 318(VI):513)
  - Two unidentified boys on horseback, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):514)
  - Bobby Bends and Joe Medicine Crow unloading a truck, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):515)
  - Lizzie Yellowtail and others sitting outside, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):516)
  - Women and children sitting outside, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):517)
  - Man and four children outside by fence, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):518)
  - Man leaning on fence, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):519)
  - House or cabin with clothesline in foreground, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):520)
  - Donnie Deernose, Agnes Yellowtail, and their adopted son, Duane Bends, circa 1950s (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):521)
  - Lodge Grass, Montana street with Baptist Church in background, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):522)
  - View of mountain peaks with snow, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):523)
  - View of building, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):524)
  - View of house in trees with car passing, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):525)
  - View of building, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):526)
  - View of urban house in trees, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):527)
  - View of building, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):528)
  - Man and woman seated on sofa, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):529)
  - Cedric Walks Over Ice and boy standing outside, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):530)
  - Man seated in armchair, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):531)
  - View of church, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):532)
  - Religious painting with priest on left, undated (Box-folder 26/59, Photo number 318(VI):533)
  - Man in shadow, house in background, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):534)
  - Man in shadow, house in background, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):535)
  - Man in shadow, house in background, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):536)
  - Chokecherries drying, undated (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):537)
  - Unloading buffalo from stock trucks, circa 1973 (Box-folder 26/60, Photo number 318(VI):538)